(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-09-02T13:31:26.560056",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
グッドイブニング！
Good evening!
マイ キュート スチューデント、チョコ！
My cute students, Choco!
はい、ということで、本日は……
So, with that said, today is...
なんと！本日9月4日で
and guess what! Today, September 4th,
ちょこ、デビューして2周年を迎えました！
marks Choco's 2nd anniversary since debut!
やったー！
Yay!
皆さん覚えてますか？
Do you all remember?
ちょこが初めて配信したこの9月4日、デビューして2年経ちました！
Choco's very first stream on September 4th... 2 years have passed since debut!
やったー！
Yay!
そしてね、2年経って、
And you know, 2 years have passed,
見てくださいみなさん！
look at this, everyone!
ちょこね、なんとアイドルになっちゃいましたー！
Choco has somehow become an idol!
えーい！
Yay!
はい、ということでね、見てみんなこれ、
So, with that said, everyone look at this,
多分ライブでしかね、はい、ライブでしかね、
you probably only see it in live shows—yeah, only in live shows,
多分ね、ちょこのこのライブ衣装見たことないと思うから、
you probably haven't seen Choco's live outfit like this before,
本日はアイドルになるちょこをみんなに見てもらいたいなって思って
so today, I wanted everyone to see Choco as an idol.
ちょっとカメラさん、アップしたからお願いします！
Hey camera-person, please zoom in!
やばくない？いつものヒールとちょっと違うの足元も。
Isn't it crazy? Even the footwear is a bit different from usual heels.
やばくない？この白のブーツもかっこいいんだけど、
Isn't it crazy? These white boots are cool too,
このニーハイもさ、いつもと違って胸のマークも入ってるの！
and these thigh-highs too—they have Choco's chest mark on them!
グラデーションめっちゃきれいじゃない？
Aren't the gradations super pretty?
ちょこ先生ウキウキ、いやウキウキでしょ！
Choco-sensei is so excited—well, of course she is!
こんなかわいいの着れたんだよ、嬉しい！
I got to wear something this cute, I'm so happy!
からのね、このスカートも超かわいいの！
And then, you know, this skirt is super cute too!
スカートからのちょっとへそ出しっていうね、おへそ見てほしい。
Showing a bit of midriff from the skirt—I want you to see my belly button.
喜ぶがいいへそフェチ！
Rejoice, belly-button fetishists!
いつもはお胸は出してるんだけど今回はお胸はなしだけど、
I usually show my chest, but this time there's no chest,
その分に見て、これ。
but instead look at this.
ちょこのこのアクセサリー。やばくない？十字架とかさ、
Choco's accessory here. Isn't it crazy? A cross and...
ちょこの羽が入ってるの！え、めっっちゃ可愛くない？
Choco's wings are on it! Eh, isn't it super cute?
これだけでも欲しいちょこ。
I'd want Choco just for this.
そうなんです今回水着衣装じゃ見れなかった人いるかな？脇も見れるんだよ、ちゃんと。
That's right, for this time, is there anyone who couldn't see the swimsuit outfit? You can see my armpits too, properly.
そう、そしてね、見て。ポニーテール！水着以来だね。
And then, look. Ponytail! It's been since the swimsuit stream.
ちょこの3Dさ、基本的にさ、すぐ削除されちゃうからさ、
Choco's 3D stuff usually gets deleted right away,
水着衣装の時しか見れなかった人いるよね。
so there are people who could only see the swimsuit outfit.
そう チョコ先生アイドル衣装だとね 見て
So Choco-sensei in her idol outfit, you see—
みて
look.
ポニーテールなんだよ
It's a ponytail!
可愛い
So cute!
似合ってるかな？
Does it suit me?
BGMがない？
There's no BGM?
ええよ
That's fine.
チョコの声を聞いてちゃんと
Listen closely to Choco's voice, okay?
可愛い本当
So cute, really!
ありがとう
Thank you!
嬉しい
I'm so happy!
そうなんですよ 柚子チョコね 2周年ということでな
That's right, Yuzuki Choco, you see, it's our 2nd anniversary.
そう 本日はちょっといろんな企画をね ちょっとご用意させていただいてるんですけど
So today, we've got all sorts of projects prepared for you,
実話ね そう チョコ いつもね そう 今初配信もないし 多分3Dお披露目も 多分アーカイブが残ってないから そう3Dはねみんなリアタイじゃないとって言って見に来てくれたと思うんだ
actually... since there's no debut stream anymore, and probably no archive for the 3D reveal either, I think everyone came to see the 3D live because they thought "If it's not live, I can't see it!"
それがね めっちゃ嬉しいんだよね
And that makes me so happy.
そう 待機してるところでさ ホロライブメンバーとかさ みんながさ
Like, while waiting, the Hololive members and everyone were like...
もうやばいよ 3時間前くらいからずっと待機待機待機待機ってねしてくれててチョコずっと見ててよ
"Ah, it's crazy!" waiting for like 3 hours beforehand, and Choco kept watching.
そうなの
That's right.
ということでね
And with that...
ま 今回は じゃあそろそろ チョコの最初の企画の方やっていこうかなって思います
Well, for this time, let's get started on Choco's first project soon.
最初の企画は なんと まあねチョコアイドルになったということでね
The first project is—what do you know? Since Choco has become an idol,
ちょっとアイドルの先輩方
some idol seniors...
いや チョコがホロライブメンバーの中で
Well, among the Hololive members, Choco—
この方たちは もう チョコが認めるアイドルだ
these people are idols that Choco herself acknowledges!
ちょっとプロデューサーをお願いして チョコをよりね アイドルにしてもらいたく
So I asked a producer to make Choco even more of an idol,
こんな企画をご用意いたしましたー！
and we've prepared this project!
タラーン！
Ta-da!
とってちょこっと撮影会！
Drop-in Chokotto Photo Session!
ということてね
And so,
初配信ぶりに あの ちょっとみんなで ちょっとチョコのアルバムを作ってもらおうと思って
for the first time since my debut stream, I thought I'd have everyone help make a Choco album.
そう こちら シャープ柚子チョコ2周年 というタグがあるんですけど こちらを今回の 柚子チョコ2周年目のアルバムの タグとして認定いたしまーす！
So, this hashtag: #YuzukiChoco2ndAnniversary—I'm officially recognizing this as the tag for the 2nd anniversary album of Yuzuki Choco!
ということでね
And so,
シャープ柚子チョコ2周年で 色々チョコ先生のね可愛いシチュエーションいっぱいついて いっぱい呟いていただきたいと思います！
with #YuzukiChoco2ndAnniversary, taking lots of cute situations of Choco-sensei, I'd love for you to post lots of them on Twitter!
まず 今回 ホロライブメンバー呼んでるんだけど じゃあちょっと1人目呼んじゃおうかな
So first, I've called Hololive members for this, so let's call the first person!
そう 1人目はね いやチョコがマジで尊敬してる人
Yeah, the first person is someone Choco genuinely respects.
そう マジでホロライブの中で チョコね 多分トップ3の中に入る尊敬してる人
Yeah, truly, within Hololive, Choco respects them enough to be in her top 3, I'd say.
ま アイドルと言えばみたいな やっぱ アイドルと言ったらさ って方が来ると思います
Well, like "speaking of idols..." Right, when you say "idol"... I think someone like that is coming.
みんな誰だか予想して見てください
Everyone try guessing who it is!
誰だろうな
Who could it be?
誰だよな
Who is it?
誰だと思う？
Who do you think?
ヤゴー？
Yagoo?
ヤゴーじゃないよ！
Not Yagoo!
なんでヤゴーなんだよ！
Why would it be Yagoo?!
ちょっと待って ちょっと待って
Wait a second, wait a second!
ホロライブで アイドルヤゴー？ ガチで？
An idol in Hololive? Yagoo? Seriously?!
え ガチで言ってるのそれ？
Wait, are you saying that for real?
いや待って待って待って待って いや考え直せ
Hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on! Think about it again.
一旦な 一旦ホロライブメンバーをみんな言える？ 大丈夫？
First off, can everyone name the Hololive members? Are you okay?
あの わため様のホロライブ言えるかな みんな聞いた？ 大丈夫？
Can you name Watame-sama's Hololive? Did everyone hear? Are you okay?
あん中 ヤゴー入ってたっけ？ 忘れちゃったけど
Was Yagoo in there? I forgot though.
いや確かに まあ ヤゴー ヤゴーさんも 多分ね あの アイドルに入るかもしれないけど
Well, true, Yagoo... Yagoo-san might also count as an idol, perhaps,
チョコ的には あの そろそろ ちょっと本物のアイドルをね みんなに魅せてあげようかなって思います
but for Choco, it's about time I showed everyone a real idol.
それではね チョコ先生！ ああーー！
And now... Choco-sensei! Aahh—!
1人目はこの方だ！
The first person is this one!
えっ、タイミング分かんなく...
Eh, I couldn't get the timing right...
いや、なんかさースーッて言ってるからさ
No, like, you kept going "whoosh,"
スタッフさんがさ、誰かさ、めちゃくちゃハキハキ話す人いるのかなって思っちゃった
I thought maybe there was someone on staff who spoke super clearly!
しけしけ、しけ、しけしました！
Dead, dead, dead silent!
ってことで1人目はこの方！自己紹介お願いします！
So the first person is her! Please introduce yourself!
はーい！
Yay!
みなさんどーも！こんあくあー！どうもみなとあくあです。
Hello everyone! Kon-Aqua! Hello, Minato Aqua here.
ちょっと、なんかハードル高くなくない？びっくりしちゃったんだけど。
Wait, isn't the bar kind of high? I got really surprised.
なんて？
What?
いや、本当に思ってること言っただけだよ。
No, I just said what I honestly thought.
え、うそ...
Eh, no way...
いやマジでさ、あくあさまのさ、マジでさ、あのライブめちゃくちゃ感動したいの、ちょこ。
No seriously, Aqua-sama, I really want to be moved by your live concerts, Choco does.
もう1人でさ、見ててさ、うわあ、うちのライブでめちゃくちゃアイドルしてるーって思って、
Watching all alone like, "Wah, she's totally being an idol at her live"...
あ、ありがと。なんか生の声を聴くとすごい、なんかうれし、ありが...
Ah, thanks. Hearing your live voice makes me so happy, thank...
今日はね、ちょこ先生をね、超アイドルにする、すればいいんでしょ？任せなさいよ。
Today, you want to turn Choco-sensei into a super idol, right? Leave it to me.
そう、ちょこさ、ちょっとアイドル感がね、全く感じられないってね、リスナーからめちゃくちゃ言われるの。
Yeah, Choco, listeners say they can't feel any idol vibes from you at all.
そうなの？
Is that so?
そうなの、芸人枠もしかして。いやなんかちょこ先生はなんか、エロと少女が混ざってるって言われて、あの、最近アイドルじゃなくね？って言われてて、
Yeah, is she in the comedian category? No, like, people say Choco-sensei is a mix of ecchi and maiden, and recently they've been saying "Aren't you not an idol anymore?"
ちょっと悪魔さまからね、そう、悪魔さまからちょっとアイドル要素ちょっといただこうかなと思って。
So, I wanted to get a little idol element from you, Aqua-sama.
まかせてくださいよ。
Leave it to me.
お願いしますよ。
Please do.
ま、まずはですね、ま、撮影会ということでね、ま、アイドルと言ったら
Well, first of all, since it's a photoshoot, when you say idol...
やっぱり、あの、こうよくハートを作ったりするんですよ、こう。ハート、手でハートって作ったりとか。
Right, you often make hearts like this, making heart shapes with your hands.
あ、ちょこ、あ、ちょっと難しそう。あ、ちょっと、なんだそのハートは！なんだそのハート、どうした！
Ah, Choco... Ah, looks a bit difficult. Ah, wait, what kind of heart is that! What is that heart, what happened!
あ、ちょっとちょっと、どんな、どんなハートがいい？どんなハートがいい？ハートしたら分かりやすいんじゃない？
Ah, wait wait, what kind of heart is good? What kind of heart? If you make a heart, it'd be easier to understand, right?
え、なんかさ、韓国のさ、韓国かなんかでさ、なんか、あの、わかる？指、指、ようきゃの、ようきゃのハートもしやがって？ようきゃのハート。あ、違うか。
Eh, like, in Korea or somewhere, you know? Finger, finger, normie heart or something? Normie heart. Ah, no.
頭の上でぴっ、あの、丸みたいなの。あ、ちょうど、あ、こっちね。
Above your head, beep, like a circle. Ah, right, ah, this side.
で、あの、足をね、足を、足を内股にするのがポイント。
And, you know, the point is to put your legs pigeon-toed.
なんかちょっと、え、え、え？
Like, wait, eh, eh, eh?
なんか、うちまたにしてるっていうの、なんか、え？てか、なんかつ...
Like, making it pigeon-toed... wait, something...
じゃあ、そのままで、顔に、顔にあの手をあてて、なんか、ほっぺたに手あてて、
Then, staying like that, put your hands on your face, on your cheeks,
ああ、わたし恥ずかしいよ、みたく、恥ずかしいよみたく！
"Ah, I'm so embarrassed," like, "I'm so embarrassed!"
どうですか？恥ずかしいよみたく。
How is that? Like "I'm so embarrassed."
え？私大丈夫かこれ？
Eh? Am I okay doing this?
あの、ちなみにちょこ先生、あの、目尻のポーズしてもらっていいですか？
Um, by the way Choco-sensei, can you do an outer-eye pose?
ちなみにになんですけど、ちょっと確認で、え、こっち？あ、こっちでは？こう？こっちでは？
By the way, just to check, eh, this side? Ah, this side? Like this? This side?
あ、いいよ、いいよ。もっと、もっとだよ、もっとだよ。グラビアアイドル、いいよ、いけるよ。
Ah, that's good, that's good. More, more, gravure idol, nice, you can do it.
本当？もっと、もっと、もっと、あ、いい！
Really? More, more, more, ah, good!
あ、いいな、クネクネしてて、あ、いい！最高ね！
Ah, nice, wriggling around, ah, good! So great!
あ、ちょっとダッチューのしてみようかな。
Ah, maybe let's try doing "Datchuu no."
ダッチューの？いいんじゃない？
"Datchuu no"? Isn't that good?
ダッチューの。
"Datchuu no."
いーね！ちょこさま完璧だよ！こう！ちょこ先生完璧だよ！
Nice! Choco-sama is perfect! Like this! Choco-sensei is perfect!
なんかカメラ目線とかもいただけたら嬉しいです。
I'd be happy if you could also look at the camera.
カメラは、やっぱもうちょっと、あの、下向きに行こうか。下、下に、下に、下に、下に行こうか。
For the camera, let's go a bit more downwards. Down, down, down, down.
アローアングルね。はいはいはいはい、ローアングルで。
Low angle, right? Yeah yeah yeah, low angle.
もう超ローでいいんじゃない？超ロー、超ローでいいんじゃない？
Isn't super low good? Super low, super low!
超ローで、あー、おー！
Super low, ah, oh!
えー！超ローでどう？もー、あー！
Eeh! How is it in super low? Mo-, ah!
なに、なに興奮してんだ、あくあ！あくあ！
What, why are you getting excited, Aqua! Aqua!
あの、もっとローできたりするんですか？あ、これ以上怒られるか。もうちょっとロー、もうちょっとローでおねがいします。
Um, can you go even lower? Ah, will you get scolded past this? A bit lower, a bit lower please.
もう寝そべるくらいローで、寝そべるぐらいロー。
So low you're lying down, low enough to lie down.
なるほど、どうかな。ちょっと良くないですか？
I see, how is it? Isn't it pretty good?
ちょっと、あー、あ、いいんじゃないですか？
Just, ah, isn't it good?
これ、これ、後ろか見とろ。
This, this, look from behind.
失礼、失礼、失礼、失礼。
Excuse me, excuse me, excuse me, excuse me.
あ、ちょっと、あ、結構いいじゃん。だめです、こんなの。
Ah, wait, ah, it's pretty good. No, not like this.
やっぱ、アイドルってさ、普通のさ、なんか、ライブで踊るアイドルもいれば、グラビアアイドルみたいなえっちなアイドルもいるわけだからね。はいはいはい。
After all, idols have various types—some dance at lives, some are gravure-style ecchi idols, right? Yeah, yeah.
ちょこ先生はね、もう、なんて言うんだろ、ちょっと撮ったら天分取れる気がする。
Choco-sensei, you know, like, if you take photos, it feels like you'll win everything.
ガッチリ？
For real?
ちょこ、天分取れる？
Choco, winning everything?
あ、あ、ちょっと、あの、センシティブなんですけど、そんなでまずいんじゃないですか？大丈夫ですか？センシティブじゃないよ。
Ah, ah, wait, um, it's sensitive, isn't this bad? Is it okay? It's not sensitive!
あの、脇がちょっとエッチです。あ、こう、大丈夫ですか？これ。
Um, your armpits are a bit ecchi. Ah, like, is this okay? This.
大丈夫だって！
It's alright!
アイドル、あのアイドルの赤井様がやってんだよプロデューサー。
An idol—the idol Akai-sama is doing it, producer!
大丈夫に決まってるじゃん！
Of course it's decided!
怒られるぞこれマジで。怒られる前にちょっと退散したいと思います。
I'm really gonna get scolded for this.
I think I'll make a quick exit before I do.
おい退散しよ！ちょっと次のやつに全部任せちゃおう。
Hey, let's retreat!
Let's leave everything to the next person.
チョコ先生2周年おめでとう！
Choco-sensei, happy 2nd anniversary!
ありがとう！赤井様もおめでとう！
Thank you! Happy anniversary to Akai-sama too!
かわいいよ！嬉しい！
So cute! I'm so happy!
ありがとう、赤井様！
Thank you, Akai-sama!
てことでね、湊と赤井様でした！
So that was Minato and Akai-sama!
いやね、もうホロライブでアイドルって言ったら…いやもうこの間のみんなライブ見たでしょ？
You know, when you say "idol" in Hololive...
I mean, you all saw the live stream the other day, right?
やばくなかった？いやもうチョコ本当にやばくて
Wasn't it amazing? No, really,
Choco was seriously amazing,
そう、めっちゃ興奮してたの1人で家で。「あー！赤井様ぁ！」って言って。
yeah, I was super excited all by myself at home.
Going, "Ah! Akai-samaaa!"
いやまじセットリストとかも最高だったししゃ、演出とかもだけど、いやまじで赤井様の歌声めっちゃいいなって思って
Man, the setlist was amazing, the production too...
I just thought Akai-sama's singing voice is so good!
おっと？そんな中に 角巻わため女なんだ けどなんかおじさんって言ってたんだけど
Oh? In the midst of all that, it's Tsunomaki Watame-onna...
wait, she said she's an old man,
わためおじじじゃった！
It was Watame-ojiji!
私参加きちゃった。
I managed to participate!
じゃあそんなわためおじさん
So, that Watame-ojisan—
いいのかな？
Is this okay?
あれ？あれ私角巻わため女なんだ けどなんかおじさんって言ってたんだけど
Huh? Wait, I'm Tsunomaki Watame-onna...
wait, she said she's an old man,
あれ？どこ？角巻わためおじさん
Huh? Where? Tsunomaki Watame-ojisan—
あ、おじさん参加してもいいのかな？
Ah, is it okay for an old man to participate too?
あ、おじさんよろしくお願いします！
Ah, old man, nice to work with you!
ってことでそんなあなたのお名前は？ ホロライブ4期生 角巻わためです！
So, what is your name?
"Hololive 4th Generation Tsunomaki Watame!"
わため角の通りのルート！角が通りのルートのやつかな？みたーい！
Watame's horn-lined route!
Is this the horn-lined route? I wanna see!
今日はね、運営さんにもちゃんと許可を取ったね、はい。ポーズがありますから。
Today, you know, we got proper permission
from management too, yes. Because there are poses.
ではまず、あの四つん這いになっていただいて
Well first, please get down on all fours—
四つん這いになる、なるほど？四つん這いになった。
Get on all fours, I see?
I got on all fours.
いいですね！そこから、両手をちょっと前に出したりとか。
Very nice! From there,
extending both hands forward a bit,
あ、地面に付く感じで。あ、そうそうそう。
Ah, touching the ground. Ah, yes, yes, yes.
伸びる感じ。あ、もっと？
Like stretching out. Ah, more?
あ、いいですね！
Ah, this is great!
横からとか見れ、あ、見れないのかな？
Can we see from the side? Ah, can we not?
あ、こっちの方が、あ、これは
Ah, this side is better... Ah, this is
横からだね。反対側のほうがいいかも。これは高度なわきぱいですよ、これは。
from the side. The other side might be better.
This is an advanced armpit-boob pose, this is.
これは高度なわきぱい。あ！腰振っていいな？
This is advanced armpit-boob.
Ah! Can I swing my hips?
腰振って。ちょっとー、これ何、購入にあたってプロデューサーに腰振ってって言われた。怒られそう。怒られる！
Swing my hips. Wait—why did the producer
tell me to swing my hips for this? I'm gonna get scolded. I'm gonna get scolded!
いやでも今回プロデューサー持ちだから大丈夫。大丈夫だよね？
But since the producer is holding it this time, it's fine.
It's fine, right?
なんでも言ってくださいて言われちゃったからね。
They told me to say anything, after all.
で、そのままで、はい。さあ、座ってもらって座る？立て膝で。
And, just like that, yes. Now, please sit—sit? With your knees up.
立て膝。あ、そう。で、両手を
Knees up. Ah, yes. And, both hands—
後頭部に。あ、そうそうそう！こういうこと？そう、で、ちょっと胸を張ってもらって。
On the back of your head. Ah, yes, yes, yes!
Like this? Yes, and puff out your chest a bit.
胸を張って
Chest puffed out—
ああ、いいですね！
Ah, this is great!
これはお上品ですね。
This is very refined.
カメラ指示とか大丈夫？それで。
Is the camera direction okay? With that.
大丈夫。あ、もうちょっとこう、横とかも見たいんだけどな。
It's fine. Ah, I want to see a bit more
from the side, too.
あ、ぐるーっと一周してく？
Ah, should we go all the way around?
あ、一周できるの？一周できるよ多分。
Ah, can we do a full circle?
We probably can do a full circle.
一周しましょうか。
Shall we do a full circle?
いいね！そこし、いいな。
Nice! That waist is nice.
あ、これはいいわきぱいとヘソもろたん。
Ah, this is a great armpit-boob and belly button.
いまのわためーしんのポーズと一緒だからね、ほぼ。
Because this is almost the same as Watameshin's pose right now.
いやほんまに。いやでもチョコ先生の方が色気が出るよ。
Seriously. No, but Choco-sensei's has more sex appeal.
本当に？
Really?
あ、そう。やっぱなんか違うんだよな。
Ah, yes. Somehow it's different.
なんか違うんだよな。私こうだもんな。
Somehow it's different. I'm like this, after all.
あ、あ、そうそう、あ、それも、あ、いいですね！
Ah, ah, yes, yes, ah, that is... Ah, this is great!
恥ずかしい顔とかできる？
Can you make an embarrassed face or something?
恥ずかしい顔？
An embarrassed face?
あ、いいじゃん！ちょっと見ないでよって言ってもらって。
Ah, that's good! Can you say "Don't look at me like that"?
ちょっと見ないでよ。
Please don't look at me...
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
おめでとうございます！
Congratulations!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you!
ということで、角待…輪っかめさまでした！
So, that was Tsunomaki... Watame-sama!
角ドリル！
Horn drill!
はい、ということでね、二人は
Right, so, those two were
美味しそうな羊でしたね。
some delicious-looking sheep.
羊がなんかおじさんになってたけど。
Though the sheep turned into an old man.
ま、3人目はね、ちょっと、角でラストなんですけど、
Now, for the third person, it'll be the last with horns...
ちょっとね、3人目はね、ちょっとアイドるっていうよりは、お笑い枠？
And for the third person, rather than being an idol, she's more like... comedy tier?
ただ波の音…
Just the sound of the waves...
グッバイ！
Goodbye!
切なさよ、切なすぎる！
Oh, the sorrow, too sorrowful!
このね、参加者は、全員マジでアイドルだと思ってめちゃめちゃバッグみたいな感じだったじゃん？
The participants all thought they were actual idols and went all out with bags and stuff, right?
どうしたの？
What happened?
いや、いや、アイドル、アイドル！
No, no, idols, idols!
あ、ヒールの中のアイドルだろ？分かってるって。
Oh, idols in heels, right? I know.
燃やしてんじゃねえよマジで！
Don't actually burn her!
3人目の方、おめでとう！
Third person, congratulations!
ありがとスバル！
Thank you, Subaru!
まさジさね、こういうね、
Actually, since this is
あのカメラ指初めてだから、
my first time doing camera direction,
今一生懸命ね、あのGoogleでググりましたセクシーポーズって。
I was frantically googling 'sexy poses' just now.
ちょっと待って待って、初めてだったの？
Wait, wait, it was your first time?
いや、初めてで、大体さ、祭りちゃんとかじゃん？祭りちゃんと、ふぶき先輩とかじゃん？
Yeah, for the first time, it's usually Matsuri-chan and Fubuki-senpai, right?
確かにな、確かに。
True, true.
ちょっとやっぱスバルね、ちょっとやっぱ
Well, Subaru, you know...
もう任せてよ、チョコ先生。
Leave it to me, Choco-sensei.
まず
First...
まずね、まず手を後ろで組みます。後ろに組む、はい。
First, clasp your hands behind your back. Clasp them behind, yes.
で、後ろ向いて、
And turn around...
後ろ向いて、振り返ってください。
Turn around and look back.
おお、いいねえ！
Oh, nice!
あ、振り返ってなくね？
Wait, didn't you turn back?
え？振り返ってよ。回り道してよ。
Huh? I did turn back. I walked around.
本当？あ、こういうことね？
Really? Oh, like this?
ああ、それ可愛い！いいじゃん、いいじゃん！
Ah, that's cute! That's good, that's good!
こういうことね？なんかつ、ちょっとね、
Like this? So...
そっから、後ろの腕をちょっとくねくねやめてもらえる、くねくねやめてもらっていいですか？
From there, um, can you stop wiggling your back arms? Can you stop wiggling?
なんかドキドキのそういう姿見ると、なんかソワソワしちゃうんでね。
Seeing you all nervous and like that makes me fidgety.
そっから、後ろの手を頭の上に。
From there, put your back hand on top of your head.
こっちか。
This side?
お、いいじゃん！え、待って、それを全身で見てみたい、スバル。
Oh, nice! Wait, I want to see that with your whole body, Subaru.
全身で？いいよ。
With your whole body? Sure.
え、待って、センスあるかも知れん、スバル。
Wait, you might have some sense for this, Subaru.
どう？
How is it?
あ、いいですねえ！
Ah, it's great!
ゆち？
Yuchi?
ゆちね？
うん。
Yeah.
良き。でね、スバルね、もう1個、そのね、これセクシーポーズでばチョコ先生じゃん？なんかスバルの最強可愛いアイドルポーズをデンジしようと思って。
Good. And Subaru, one more thing, since Choco-sensei is doing sexy poses, I thought I'd teach you Subaru's ultimate cute idol pose.
あ、ガチ？
Oh, seriously?
スバルあの可愛さが表現できるってこと？
You can express Subaru's cuteness?
え、うれしい！
Yay, I'm happy!
そうだよ。じゃあまず、参辰のポーズをとってもらっていいですか？
That's right. So first, can you take the Sanchin pose?
参辰？画像ググったでしょ？
Sanchin? You googled it, didn't you?
参辰、そんな膝つけちゃダメだよ、もっと開かないと。
Sanchin, you shouldn't bend your knees like that, you have to spread them more.
ガチでやるの、これ？
Are you seriously doing this?
全身越しやめろ、参辰に失礼だ、もっと腰、腰立てて！
Stop looking at my whole body, it's disrespectful to Sanchin, lift your hips more!
あ、そうそうそう。
Ah, right, right.
それで、失礼だわお前。
You're being rude.
そのまま手を、手を、こう、手首を合わせるようにして、あごのところ持ってきて。
From there, bring your hands, your wrists together, and bring them to your chin.
で、グ、手グーにして、
And make your fists,
で、あの、あごに手当てて、で
and put your hand on your chin, and...
あ、はいはいはい。
Ah, yes yes yes.
そうそうそう！
Right, right, right!
でスバルが、参辰って言ったらコーって言って、チョコ先生。これは覚悟だから、最強可愛い、いい？分かった。
And when Subaru says 'Sanchin', you go 'Koo!', Choco-sensei. This is a commitment, ultimate cuteness, okay? Got it.
よし、いくよ。せーの、参辰、コーッ！
Alright, here we go. Ready, Sanchin, Koo!
いや、やめてよ！スバルに、スバルにそんなのさせないでよ！
Hey, stop it! Don't make Subaru do that kind of thing!
いやでも可愛い！可愛いよ、チョコ先生。
No, but it's cute! It's cute, Choco-sensei.
で、最強可愛いよ。
And ultimate cuteness.
いやマジでさ、スバルと話してるとさ、スバル語が映るんだよな。
Seriously, talking to Subaru makes Subaru-speak rub off on me.
いや、スバル語じゃねえよ！語じゃねえよ！
Hey, that's not Subaru-speak! It's not -go!
え、あと、純粋に両手広げておいでってしてほしい。
Um, also, purely, I want you to spread both arms and say 'Come here'.
あ、わかったわかった。
Ah, got it, got it.
カメラ目線で、いいですか？
Looking at the camera, is that okay?
おいで。あー可愛い！いいじゃん、いいじゃん！
Come here. Aah, cute! That's good, that's good!
からの、参辰！参辰コー！
Then, Sanchin! Sanchin Koo!
いや、やめてよ！
Hey, stop it!
いやマジで、もうこういうとこマジ好き、チョコ先生。
Seriously, I really love these aspects of you, Choco-sensei.
バカすんなよ
Don't be an idiot.
チョコ先生ね、次から可愛いポーズ困ったらこれ使って一緒に今度写真撮ろうね。
Choco-sensei, if you're ever stuck for a cute pose, use this and let's take a picture together!
ああ、3って言ったら？
Ah, when I say "three"?
こわっ！
Scary!
ちなみにこれ電車の中でやるとマジね足フラつかないからオススメ。
By the way, doing this on a train really stops your legs from wobbling, so I recommend it.
じゃあね、おめでとう！
Well then, congratulations!
なんで電車の中でやってんの、お前！
Why are you doing that on a train?!
バイバーイ！バイバーイ！
Bye-bye! Bye-bye!
やばいだろう。
That's dangerous, right?
いやマジで、スバルはね、電車の中で「こっ！」ってやってるみたいでね。
Seriously, it seems Subaru does "Ko!" inside the train.
はい。
Yes.
たーだーなーみーのーとー
Ta-da-na-mi-no-to...
でしたー！
...was it!
はあ、やばい、暑い、ちょっとチョコ、やばいわ。
Hah, man, it's hot, Choco, this is bad.
今のさ、撮影会で、やばい、体力の2/3もっていかれたんだけど、七草粥は食い過ぎてやばいわ。 ということでね、次の企画に移りたいと思います。 ちょっとね、チョコ、ちょっと体力やられちゃったから、ちょっと準備とあの休憩を含めてちょっと、 ちょっとね、さっきの「たーだーなーみーのーとー」も出てくる。 準備中、よろしくお願いします。
That photo session just now took away 2/3 of my stamina, and eating too much seven-herb porridge is bad. With that said, I'd like to move on to the next segment. Choco got her stamina zapped, so including prep and a break... the "tada-nami-no-to-" from earlier is coming back out. While preparing, please treat me well.
映像スバル！スバルもっと燃えろ！燃えろ燃えろ燃えろ燃えろ燃えろ！
Video Subaru! Subaru, burn more! Burn, burn, burn, burn, burn!
あ、ごめんなさい、すいません。
Ah, I'm sorry, excuse me.
はい、ということでね、みなさまただいまです。
Yes, with that said, everyone, I'm back.
はい、ということで次の企画の方に移ってまいりたいと思います。
Yes, with that said, I'd like to move on to the next segment.
どうしたのみんなそんなクソって？ちょっとよくわかんないなチョコ。
What's with everyone acting like that? Choco doesn't really get it.
はい、ということで、次の企画は、ちょっとね、とある方々にちょっとチョコがおねがいして、 ちょっとね、とある台本を書いていただきましたということで、次の企画はこちら！
Yes, with that said, the next segment is—Choco asked certain people to write a script for her, so the next segment is right here!
プロポーズコーナー 緑仙編
Proposal Corner: Ryushen Edition
まず一人目は、まあ、2時3時のね、まあ脚本家と言ったらこの方でしょう。
First up is, well, when you talk about Nijisanji's scriptwriter, it has to be this person.
竜仙に、今回はちょっとプロポーズ台本をね、ねお竜仙お願いお願い書いて書いて書いて書いて！って言ってね
Asking Ryushen for a proposal script this time, saying "Hey Ryushen, please, please write it, write it, write it!"
ちょっと、
Hold on,
竜神プロデュースのプロポーズ台本のほうね、
for the proposal script produced by Ryushen,
今回はチョコが演じさせていただこうと思います！
this time Choco will be acting it out!
いやマジでね、竜神の台本、いやマジ神すじるからね、
Seriously, Ryushen's script is seriously divine,
ちょっとね皆さんちょっと楽しみにしててください。
so everyone please look forward to it.
そうなんです、この見通りチョコは頼んでやった。
That's right, just like you see, Choco asked him to.
おねがい、つって。
Saying "Please."
いやマジで竜神優しいでさ、いやめっちゃ心良くさ、
Seriously, Ryushen is so kind, and so willingly—
あ、いいよチョコ先生みたいな
"'Oh sure, Choco-sensei'—"
感じでね、そう、引き受けてくれたんですよ。そう。
Like that, yeah, they agreed to do it. Yeah.
マジ優しい。うん。
Seriously kind. Yeah.
ということで、じゃあ早速やっていこうかな。
With that said, let's get right into it.
まこの後ね、ま他のホロライブメンバーも書いてくれた台本も出てくるので、ぜひぜひ皆さまちょっと誰が書いてくれたのかワクワクしながらね、
Well, after this, scripts written by other Hololive members will also be coming out, so everyone, while wondering excitedly who wrote it,
待ってて、ぜひ聞いてみてくださいということで
please wait and definitely give it a listen.
それではそんな竜神台本まで3、3、2、2、1、1、アート！
With that, until Ryushen's script... 3, 2, 1, Action!
もう、出番いちゃった。
My turn's already up.
正直ね、
Honestly,
すごい緊張してる。
I'm so nervous.
こんなにたくさん人の前で歌うんだもん、今まで練習してきた成果、ちゃんと出せるかなって。
Since I'm singing in front of so many people, I wonder if I can properly show the results of all my practice.
え？チョコ先生らしくない？
Eh? Doesn't sound like Choco-sensei?
君の前だからかな？ギャップでもっと好きになっちゃった？
Is it because I'm in front of you? Did you fall for the gap even more?
それともこんな弱気な先生は嫌いになっちゃった？
Or did you come to hate a teacher acting so weak like this?
なんて、君はきっと優しいから、どんなチョコでも受け入れてくれるんだろうけど。
Just kidding, since you're surely kind, you'd probably accept whatever kind of Choco I am, but—
君にだけ甘えちゃだめかな？
Can I lean on you just a little bit?
大丈夫、君が味方でいてくれるなら、チョコ頑張れるよ。
It's alright, if you're on my side, Choco can do her best.
それに、ここまで連れてってくれたみんなにも、かっこいい先生見せてあげなくちゃね。
Besides, I have to show a cool teacher side to everyone who brought me this far, right?
あのさ、
Um, you know,
これからはチョコのこと、アイドルとしてじゃなくて、一人の女の子として見てくれないかな？
from now on, instead of as an idol, could you look at Choco as just one girl?
なんて、嘘嘘嘘嘘！もうこんなこと言うつもりなかったのに、もう！
No way, no, no, no! I didn't mean to say something like this, ugh!
みんなが待ってるからって、話してくれないと先生いけないよ？
Everyone's waiting, so if you don't talk to me, teacher can't do this, okay?
ずっと話さないでいてくれる？
Will you stay by my side without speaking forever?
チョコのことずっとそばで見守ってくれるって、
Promise me you'll watch over Choco close by forever.
約束して。先生との約束、ね？行ってきます。
A promise with the teacher, okay? I'll be going now.
同じ未来を見ていた
We wanted to see the same future,
あの夢を手にした
and made that dream our own.
それぞれ違う
With our respective,
ココロで走れ go
different hearts, run, go!
どこを見ても真っ暗な場所に芽生えていた
Sprouting in a pitch-black place wherever I looked,
ほんの小さな希望にこの瞳奪われた
my eyes were stolen by a tiny hope.
不安で揺れるココロを上手くチューニングして
Tuning my shaky, anxious heart just right,
ほんの小さな勇気を振り絞っていたよ
I mustered up a tiny bit of courage.
諦めの文字デリートして進む
Deleting words of surrender, I push forward,
苦しいときも
even in painful times,
もう私はひとりじゃないから
because I'm not alone anymore.
だからもっと夢追いかけたい ワクワク止まらない
So I want to keep chasing my dreams, my excitement never stops.
想像超えてく 世界見せてあげる
I'll show you a world that surpasses imagination.
アクセスしてみたい 後悔なんてさせない
I want to log in, and I won't let you have any regrets.
それぞれ違う ココロで走れ go
With our respective, different hearts, run, go!
仮想の空に輝く 眩しい想いは
The dazzling feelings shining in the virtual sky
見たことのない光を 現実に届けるよ
bring a light never seen before into reality.
いつも聴こえるエールは ここにキャプチャーして
Capturing the cheers I always hear right here,
また新しい光を 探したくなるよ
it makes me want to search for a new light.
君の笑顔は 保存して進む
I save your smile and keep moving forward,
悲しいときに 見返すよ
looking back at it when I feel sad.
チカラが湧くから
Because it gives me strength.
胸を張って夢追いかけたい 奇跡の物語
I want to chase my dreams with pride, a miraculous story.
一緒に作ろう
Let's create it together,
終わらない夢を
a never-ending dream,
誰一人欠かせない
with no one left behind,
愛が舞い込んだこの世界
this world where love has fluttered down.
それぞれ違う ココロで彩れ
Color it with our respective, different hearts.
悲しいときも 寂しいときも
Even when I'm sad, even when I'm lonely,
信じ合えるものがある
there are things we can believe in together.
忘れずにこの鼓動 鳴らし続けたい
I want to keep making this heartbeat echo without forgetting.
終わらない世界に 溢れ出すよ笑顔たち
Smiles overflow into a never-ending world.
憧れの舞台立ちたい
I want to stand on the stage of my admiration,
らしく輝きたい
and shine just like myself.
時に涙して また笑い合いたい
Sometimes shedding tears, and smiling together again.
同じ未来を見たいの あの夢を手にした
I want to see the same future, and make that dream our own.
踏み出そう 奇跡の一歩を
Let's take a miraculous step forward.
息切らして夢追いかけたい
Catching my breath, I want to chase my dreams,
ワクワク止まらない
my excitement never stops.
想像超えてく 世界見せてあげる
I'll show you a world that surpasses imagination.
アクセスしてみたい
I want to log in,
後悔なんてさせない
and I won't let you have any regrets.
それぞれ違う ココロで作るworld
Creating a world with our respective, different hearts.
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
どうでした？チョコの滅びの歌
How was it? Choco's song of destruction.
どうも、ホロライブ1滅びの歌と言われた女、癒月ちょこです。
Hello, I'm Yuzuki Choco, known as Hololive's number one song of destruction.
いやね、ちょっとはね、いや 多分一番最初に歌った時よりは上達してると思います。
Well, you know... I think I've improved a bit compared to when I first sang it.
ということでね、ちょっとちょこ先生ね、いや今頑張ってさ、アイドルなんだなって思ったらね
So, you know, Choco-sensei... when I thought, "Ah, I'm working hard as an idol right now,"
ちょっと次の企画がね、あの1年前チョコ覚えているでしょうか？1年前...
the next project is... do you remember Choco from a year ago? A year ago...
3D配信でやった
I did a 3D stream,
あの赤い企画、そう
that red project—yes,
レッドカーペット企画をね、この次やろうと思うのでね
the red carpet project, we'll be doing next, so
ぜひね、ちょこ先生頑張ったっていう人はね、
if you think "Choco-sensei worked hard,"
ちょこにレッドカーペット届けてください。
please send a red carpet to Choco.
それでは次の企画まで
And now, until the next project...
3、2、1、アート！
3, 2, 1, start!
はーいということで、
Hi there, so,
さて皆様、ここで間違い探しです。
Now everyone, here is a spot-the-difference game.
いつものちょこと今までと
There is something different
どこか違うところがあります。さてどこでしょう？
about Choco from usual. Where could it be?
ということで皆様、近くに寄って
So everyone, please come closer
ぜひともね確かめていただきたいと思います。
and check it out for yourselves.
それではレッドカーペット近くスタートです。
Now, the red carpet proximity starts.
ちょこのもとに来て
Come to Choco
この間違い探しをぜひとも見つけてください。
and please find this spot-the-difference.
そうこちらねスパチャが投げられるごとにね
Yes, in this project, whenever a super chat is thrown,
レッドカーペットがちょこの方に近づいてくるという企画でございます。
the red carpet gets closer to Choco.
ぜひともちょこのもとに皆さんも来て、ちょこのいつもと違ったちょこを見ていただけたらと思います。
I hope everyone comes to Choco and sees a different Choco than usual.
ちょこ先生可愛い本当に？
Choco-sensei is so cute, really?
近づいてる近づいてる。
It's getting closer, getting closer.
や、マジでみてほしいずっと。
Seriously, I want you to keep watching.
ありがとうございます！ありがとうございます！先生大好き本当に！嬉しい。
Thank you! Thank you! I really love you, teacher! I'm so happy.
レッドカーペットが続いていく。おっと？
The red carpet continues. Oh?
ありがとうございます！レッドカーペットがどんどん近づいてくる。
Thank you! The red carpet is getting closer and closer.
みんなちょことはのお約束覚えて
Everyone, remember your promise with Choco...
聞こえてますか?
Can you hear me?
2周年おめでとうございます!
Thank you so much for the 2-year anniversary!
ありがとうございます!
Thank you so much!
お久しぶりのレッドカーペット,chocoの元まで届いてくれるかな?
I wonder if the red carpet will reach Choco's base at last.
2周年おめでとうございます!ありがとう!嬉しい!
Happy 2nd anniversary! Thank you, I'm so happy!
どんどん近づいてきてる｡
It's getting closer and closer.
おめでとう!ありがとう!メンバーシップもありがとうございます!
Thank you for the congratulations and memberships!
choco先生好き?本当?もっと近くでchocoのこと見てほしいな｡
Do you really like Choco-sensei? I want you to come closer and look at her.
すごいなんか新郎さんが近づいてってレベルたい一歩一歩｡
It's like the groom is getting closer step by step.
あれ?新郎?しっぷ?あれ､教会の前で待ってるのってどっちだっけ?
Wait, which groom is waiting in front of the church?
あともう少し!届けこの想い!chocoは待ってるよ｡
Just a little more and it will reach you, this feeling. Choco is waiting.
choco後ろ下がってないよ!後ろ下がってないよ!chocoはここにいるよ｡んー?
Wait, Choco isn't backing up! Choco is right here!
新郎が待ってる?あ､大丈夫｡みんな安心って結婚式次第はchocoが出してあげる｡
Shinto is waiting? Oh, don't worry, Choco will get the results for you.
あともう少し｡あともうちょっとなの｡
Just a little more, just a little bit more.
choco先生のところまで行きますね!早くして?chocoここで待ってるね｡
I'll go all the way to Choco-sensei. Speak up! Choco is waiting here.
あともう少し｡あともう少しなの｡
Just a little more, just a little more.
Throw super chat and connect Choco-sensei to the red carpet.
Come on!
Thank you super chat, thank you premium, thank you support.
2周年おめでとうございます!ありがとう!
Happy 2nd anniversary! Thank you!
ほら!chocoの胸まで飛び込んでおいで!
Look, come into Choco's chest!
やっと来てくれたね｡
You finally did it!
見て見て!ねえ､chocoのところ何が変わったか分かる?
Look, look! Can you tell what changed about Choco?
届いた!やったー!えいっ!やったー!やっと来てくれたー!
It arrived, yay! Yay!
ありがとう!
Thank you!
みんな!ありがとう!2周年でーす!2周年が経ったよお!
Everyone, thank you! It's our 2nd anniversary! We made it to 2 years!
やったー!ということで､皆様chocoは何で変わったこと起こる?
Yay! So, everyone, why did Choco...
見て見て見て見て!前回の3D放送とchoco変わったところがあるでしょ?分かるかな?
Look, look, look! There's a difference between the last 3D broadcast and Choco, right? Can you tell?
そう､これで私はばんそらない｡そう､完全個体を手に入れたのだ｡
So, with this, I'm fully dressed. So, I got the complete individual.
みんなのもの､もっと可愛くなった?本当に?いや､まあchoco先生可愛いからね｡うん｡
Everyone's stuff... did it get cuter, really? Well, Choco-sensei is cute, right? Hmm.
じゃあ､そんな可愛いchocoにね､ちょっとみんなに伝えたいことがあって､その前に
So, to that cute Choco, I want to tell everyone something, but before that,
プラパローず近く第2弾ということで
Plaparo close, Vol. 2!
次はね､ホロライブメンバーのchoco先生の大好きなオカタに台本を考えていただいたの!誰が作った台本か?ぜひぜひね｡
Next is, Choco-sensei's favorite cast member thought of the script. Who wrote the script? Please, please!
皆様聞いて当ててみてください。
Everyone, listen and try to guess.
それでは…
Now then...
プロポーズ企画まで332211あーと！
Until the proposal segment, 3, 3, 2, 2, 1, 1, start!
うーん…
Mhm...
あれ？寝ちゃっててたのかな？
Huh? Did I fall asleep?
うーん…
Ugh...
おはよう。
Good morning.
私たち疲れたみたいね。
It looks like we're exhausted.
こんな時間まで寝ちゃってたわ。
We slept in until this time.
せっかくの休日なのにね。
Even though it's our day off.
でもたまにはこういう日もあるかしら。
But I suppose days like this are nice too.
え？
Hm?
何？
What?
なんかソワソワしてる。
You seem all fidgety.
え？
Hm?
左手？
Your left hand?
え？
Huh?
指輪は？
The ring?
婚約指輪渡したりする？
Do people exchange engagement rings?
ちょっと待って！こんなの聞いてない！
Wait a minute! I didn't hear about this!
嬉しい。ちょこでいいの？
I'm so happy. Are you sure you're okay with Choco?
もういつから考えてたのよ。
Just how long have you been thinking about this?
ってことは途中から追ってたのね？
That means you've been following it since halfway through?
サプライズ？
A surprise?
嬉しいわ。そういうところも好きよ。
I'm so happy. I love that side of you too.
返事聞きたい。
I want to hear your answer.
焦らないの。
Don't rush me.
何を今更。キスでそんなにびっくりしてるのよ。
What are you saying now? Why are you so surprised by a kiss?
私でよければ…
If you're okay with me...
よろしくお願いします。
Please take care of me.
大好きよ。
I love you so much.
はい！ということで…
Yes! And so...
この台本は私の大好きなメル様が、夜空メル様が考えてくれました！
this script was thought up by my absolute favorite, Mel-sam—Yozora Mel-sama!
私の本妻メル様…
My true wife, Mel-sama...
いやもう最高の台本だよな、マジで。
Seriously, this is the absolute best script ever, for real.
とやっ…ほら、カメラに向かってやってんぞ、あいつ。
Toya... Look, she's doing it toward the camera, that guy.
いや、いい仕事する、マジで。やはりメル様は天才ヴァンパイアだった。
Man, she does such good work, seriously. As expected, Mel-sama is a genius vampire.
ということでね、皆様…
And so, everyone...
チョコと…結婚してくれますか？
will you... marry Choco?
ということで、ゆづきちょこ2周年ということで、な、な、な、な、なんと！
And so, to celebrate Yuzuki Choco's 2nd anniversary, wh-wh-wh-what?!
こちら！ゆづきちょこ活動2周年記念グッズが発売開始！
Here! Yuzuki Choco's 2nd Anniversary Goods are now on sale!
ということでね、いやマジこの内容がマジでやばいからちょっと見てほしい。すいません、ちょっとね、お写真いただいたんでね、こちら
So yeah, seriously, the contents of this are so crazy you've gotta check it out. Sorry, I got some photos sent to me, so here—
の方を見ていただきたいと思います。
I'd like you to take a look at...
お願いします！
Please!
ということで、ゆず...ごにん、やった！やった！わあ！
And so, Yuzu... oops, Yada! Yay! Wow!
ということでね、癒月ちょこ活動二周年記念グッズということで、なんと、な、な、なんと、皆様！
And so, for Yuzuki Choco's 2nd anniversary merchandise, guess, gu-gu-guess what, everyone!
この、ちょコの、見てください、この角にある指輪は...
Look at this, on Choco's horns, this ring here...
これね、何の指輪かって言ったら、ちょこが愛する人と契約をする時にね、
What ring is this, you ask? When Choco makes a pact with the person she loves,
この、相方にこの片方の指輪をあげるんだけど、その、癒月ちょこ刻印入り結婚指輪！
she gives one of these rings to her partner, and that is... the Yuzuki Choco Engraved Marriage Ring!
ちなみにちょこの刻印ちゃんと入ってます。ちゃんと入ってます。
By the way, Choco's engraving is properly on it. It's properly on it.
と、このちょこの角のね、リングスタンド！
And Choco's horn-shaped ring stand!
そして、癒月ちょことの契約書ということで、癒月ちょこ婚姻届！の活動二周年記念グッズが、
And as Choco's contract, the Yuzuki Choco Marriage Certificate! These 2nd anniversary goods...
ただいま概要欄に貼ってあるね、ブースの裏からただいま絶賛、発売開始されましたー！
...are currently available for purchase right now from the Booth link in the description!
ホロライブ初の結婚指輪のグッズ、ずっと言ってたの2年間！なんとね、それが...
Hololove's very first marriage ring merch—I've been talking about it for 2 whole years! And guess what, it...
ちょこのわがままが通って、今回はね、ただいま発売開始となりましたー！
...Choco's selfishness prevailed, and sales have just started right now!
ただ皆様、1つお気をつけください。このグッズ、期間限定販売でございます。
However, everyone, please keep one thing in mind. This merch is available for a limited time only.
そうなんです。なので、期間内にちゃんと...忘れずに購入してくださいね。ちょことの契約書。
That's right. So please make sure to purchase it within the period without forgetting. Choco's contract.
そうなんです。あの、社畜のTシャツはこないだ出したばっかのやつもブースで発売してるんだけど、社畜のTシャツはね、ぶっちゃけね、ケダマとか付いたらちゃんと、あの、もう1枚買えるようにね、ちょこずっと売りっぱにしてあるんだけど、
That's right. Um, for the corporate slave t-shirt, the one I just released recently is also on sale in the Booth, but for the corporate slave t-shirt, to be honest, if it gets fuzz or anything on it, so you can buy another one, Choco's kept it on sale continuously, but...
こちら、期間限定販売なんで、期間内にちょことと皆さんちゃんと契約してくださいね。
...this is a limited-time sale, so please make sure to properly make your contract with Choco within the period.
ということで、皆さんちょこの2周年放送いかがだったでしょうか？
And so, everyone, how was Choco's 2nd-anniversary broadcast?
デビューして から本日で2年目を迎えます癒月ちょこ！
Yuzuki Choco, celebrating 2 years since her debut today!
これからも応援のほどよろしくお願いします！
Thank you for your continued support!
ちょこはね、みんなが応援してくれる限り、頑張ってお勉強していくので、
Choco, as long as everyone supports her, will work hard and keep studying,
ぜひぜひね、ちょこの生徒さんにでるのね、こちらのほうご覧ください。
so please, be sure to check that out, for Choco's students.
それでは皆様、またお会いしましょう。
Well then everyone, let's meet again.
バイバーイ！シャープ癒月ちょこ2周年でぜひぜひつぶやいてください。あとでいっぱいリサーチしていきます。
Bye-bye! Be sure to tweet with hashtag Yuzuki Choco 2nd Anniversary. I'll be checking all of them later.
またねー！
See ya!